Violeta Sol Arias Hours

Full Stack Developer

Salta – Salta, Argentina (+54) 9 3875377584

violehours@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/violetasolariashours/ GitHub: https://github.com/VioleHours Porfolio: https://violetahours.vercel.app/

TECH SKILLS: Javascript, Typescript, Python

FRONT-END: HTML5, Css3, ReactJs, ReduxJs, NextJs, TailwindCss, Angular

BACK-END: NodeJs, Express, Sequelize

DATABASES: PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Firebase

TOOLS: Git/GitHub, VSCode, VisualStudio, Slack, Trello AGILE: Scrum

ABOUT ME

I am a Full Stack developer with a background in Audiovisual Production. I have experience in both Frontend and Backend development, and possess skills in agile methodologies, GIT, and data structures. In addition to technical skills such as Javascript, React, NodeJs, and Angular, I have worked on individual and group projects, which has helped me develop soft skills such as effective communication, teamwork, adaptability, and problem-solving.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Countries Pl

Academic Experience - Henry Bootcamp

Individual Project

In this project, I developed a Single Page Application (SPA) about countries and activities, where users can create, assign, and delete activities. It also includes combined filters, pagination, and controlled forms, among other features...

Front: React, Redux, Css Back: NodeJs, Express

Database: PostgreSQL y Sequelize

Full Stack Web Developer – PF e-latam

Academic Experience - Henry Bootcamp

Our project is an innovative e-commerce platform designed specifically for the dynamic and vibrant Latin American market. This platform serves as a virtual marketplace where administrators oversee business operations, and users interact with a wide range of products, reviews, and ratings. Users have the freedom to explore an extensive catalog of products and make informed purchasing decisions.

Front: React, ReduxToolkit, Css, Vite

Back: NodeJs, Express.

Database: PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE.

Odoo Developer

May 2023 - Present

InkuA · Internship Contract

Developing websites for NGOs using Odoo and Python primarily.

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

Academic Experience - Henry Bootcamp

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

- Coordinating a group of students to facilitate integration into the study team.
- Assisting in exercise resolution and promoting group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Proposing ideas for improving Bootcamp processes.

Camera Assistant

Nov 2018 - Mar 2020

Universidad Católica de Salta

- Responsible for the proper maintenance of the camera during filming.
- Handling television studio cameras for the subjects of Broadcasting and Production and Direction for Radio and Television careers.

EDUCATION

- UX/UI Design. Codo a Codo. 198 hours of theoretical and practical training. Aug 2023 Present.
- Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours of theoretical and practical training. Oct 2022 Jul 2023.
- Bachelor's Degree in Image and Sound. Universidad Católica de Salta. 19/50 subjects approved. 2018 2020.

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Fashion Design/Personal Image Consulting. Instituto de alta moda y belleza integral Roberto Piazza Salta. 2021-2022.
- Production and Direction for Radio and Television. Universidad Católica de Salta. 2019-2020.

LANGUAGES

• English B2 - Intermediate.